<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>With Entropy</title>
    <link>https://www.withentropy.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on With Entropy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 14:19:18 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.withentropy.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Couple Minutes</title>
      <link>https://www.withentropy.com/blog/2025-04-18-couple_minutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 14:19:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.withentropy.com/blog/2025-04-18-couple_minutes/</guid>
      <description>I planned a trip to Puerto Rico about a month ago with my girlfriend. Five days off, extending the long weekend to snorkel, hike El Yunque, and take a tropical cocktail-making class. The day of our flight, the island suffered a full blackout. I only found out four hours before our flight was supposed to take off. In fact, I almost missed it: no alerts, no emails, just a stray glance at Bloomberg news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Banal Paradise</title>
      <link>https://www.withentropy.com/blog/2025-04-13-a_banal_paradise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 12:58:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.withentropy.com/blog/2025-04-13-a_banal_paradise/</guid>
      <description>One of my core beliefs about human nature is that what makes us happy is not what we consciously want. We&amp;rsquo;re built to desire struggle, and thrive in well-defined systems in which we work towards a reward. I&amp;rsquo;m not talking banal office &amp;ldquo;work&amp;rdquo; for a paycheck, but rather something analogous to hunting. This is part of why I enjoy my job so much, but that is a story for another time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Friend</title>
      <link>https://www.withentropy.com/blog/2024-02-16-a_friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 20:16:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.withentropy.com/blog/2024-02-16-a_friend/</guid>
      <description>Absolutely within ten years, all of us will be conversing with AI more than with other people. The topic of AI and its impact on jobs and market capitalizations and whatever have been beat to death, but I think this point is flying over the head of the average person.
I&amp;rsquo;m certain that in ten years, coming home from work will look more like Blade Runner 2049 than anything else. Less sex and Ana de Armas, but the core concept will remain the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Fucking Impossible to Stay Healthy</title>
      <link>https://www.withentropy.com/blog/2023-10-24-its_impossible_to_stay_healthy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 18:02:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.withentropy.com/blog/2023-10-24-its_impossible_to_stay_healthy/</guid>
      <description>My college physical life was a bit strange. I worked out(weights) nearly every day, except that I basically didn&amp;rsquo;t move from my chair at any other point in time. Food was a block away, and I nearly never went to class. The few times I did, I would use an electric scooter. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t like I was a health nut, but I generally kept my weight between 175-180lb as a 6&#39;0 male.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I Should be Doing</title>
      <link>https://www.withentropy.com/blog/2023-10-09-what_i_should_be_doing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 19:16:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.withentropy.com/blog/2023-10-09-what_i_should_be_doing/</guid>
      <description>I think my base nature is to not be appreciative of the things I truly have. Every day, I think about the things that I could be doing. I could be slaving away at an art school, working to perfect my craft to create my masterpiece someday. I could be doing a PhD, serving my years to be part of the AI revolution that&amp;rsquo;s hopefully coming. I could be a writer, searching for some type of meaning that I could impart on my readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://www.withentropy.com/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.withentropy.com/aboutme/</guid>
      <description>About me Contact: withentropy at gmail</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
